(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
本日はホロライブゲーマーズ結成記念ライブ、げまずえでぃしょん！へお越しいただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to the Hololive Gamers Anniversary Live: Gamers Edition today!
お客様へご案内いたします。こちらの配信は、ハッシュタグ...
We have an announcement for our guests. For this stream...
「#ホロゲマズ結成記念LIVE2024」をつけて、Xへのスクリーンショット投稿などを推奨しております。
...we encourage you to post screenshots on X using the hashtag '#HololiveGamersAnniversaryLIVE2024'.
ピンポンパンポーン。迷子のお知らせです。
Ding-dong-dang-dong. This is a lost child announcement.
おにぎりのかぶりものをした大人の人が来ています。
There is an adult here wearing an onigiri headpiece.
お友達はお迎えに来てあげてね。
Friends, please come and pick them up.
すこん部の皆、ミオファの皆、おにぎりゃーの皆、ころねすきの皆...
Sukonbu-members, Mio-fa, Onigiri-ya, Korone-suki...
手を取り合って生きていきましょう。
...let's all take each other's hands and live together.
それではまもなく開演です。もうちょびっと待っててね。
Well then, the show will start shortly. Please wait just a little longer.
みゃーみゃーみゃんころじーで 人類みゃっ！？とびだーん！
Mya-mya-myancology, humanity Mya!? Jump out!
いままでのあらすじ...
The story so far...
なんか爆発して 爆発すればいいと思いました。ザッパーン！
Something exploded, and I thought it should just explode. Splash!
たとえば磁石 砂の中にも...
For example, magnets in the sand...
宇宙人が地球征服に来ていた。
Aliens were coming to conquer the Earth.
ちょっと不便だ おっきいの出してよ。
It's a bit inconvenient, bring out the big one.
戦艦大和 だれか動かして！
Battleship Yamato, someone move it!
ざばばだば 牛乳飲んで。
Zababadaba, drink some milk.
ざばばだば 早めに就寝。
Zababadaba, go to bed early.
ざばばだば 大人はきっと こっそり変身。
Zababadaba, adults surely transform in secret.
怪人だー！
It's a monster!
総統だー！
It's the leader!
制服だー！
It's a uniform!
はーめーはーめー波ー！
Ka-me-ha-me-ha!
冥土 冥土 冥土のお土産。
Hades, Hades, a souvenir from Hades.
そりゃ桃源郷のそっくりさんだ。
That's a look-alike of Shangri-La.
タイムマシン 手作りしました。
I handmade a time machine.
時歩少女 追い越した。
The girl who walks through time, I overtook her.
退屈退屈退屈座りで。
Bored, bored, sitting in a bored way.
膝の匂いを嗅ぐと落ち着いた。
I felt calm when I smelled my knees.
タイムマシン 一人乗りでしょ。
The time machine is a single-seater, right?
歴史塗り替えたら 総集編！
If we rewrite history, it's a recap episode!
君はつまり 感情ばっかりで。
In short, you're just full of emotions.
事をさらに 複雑にしておる。
You're making things even more complicated.
君はすでに 傍観者なのだと。
That you are already just a bystander.
いままでのあらすじ
The story so far
言えば淡いゆめか。
Is it a faint dream, so to speak?
完璧な馬鹿だ。
I'm a complete fool.
恋ゆえに
Because of love,
頭ゆらんで
my head is spinning,
心ゆだねて
I entrust my heart,
さだめのそぞろに ほとばしる
surging in the restlessness of fate.
巻いて巻いて巻いたらいらない
Roll it, roll it, if it's rolled, I don't need it.
むせんぶ
A dream of nothingness.
森よ森よ森のどんぐり
Oh forest, oh forest, the acorns of the forest,
拾い集めたあと虫はわくよ
after gathering them, bugs will crawl.
年は年を追い越してゆく
Years overtake the years,
それも当たり前の境界線
that too is a natural boundary line.
表裏は裏が表で
Front and back, the back is the front,
意外腹黒さが最小値
surprisingly, the black-heartedness is at its minimum.
みゃみゃみゃんころじーで人類みゃつりあん！
Mya-mya-myancology, human festival, an!
にゃにゃにゃんころじーで生類にゃ〜ん！
Nya-nya-nyancology, living creatures, nya~n!
きみが好きだ
I like you.
愛してる
I love you.
気持ち悪いって
That's gross.
ぶしなき！
Ugly crying!
無茶苦茶言うな！
Don't talk nonsense!
愛しましょう！
Let's love!
優しく言うな！
Don't say it so gently!
続きは？
What's next?
続かない！
It's not continuing!
Sorry, sorry, sorry, Solitude.
周り敵だらけで散歩し
Walking around surrounded by enemies,
Solitude, Sorry, Sorry.
浮き輪つぶしたままエア水泳
Air swimming with a deflated floatie.
Solitude, 迷宮はソリチュード
Solitude, the labyrinth is Solitude,
そりゃもうジャングリラに行っちゃえば
well, just head off to Jungrila.
Solitude, 迷宮はソリチュード
Solitude, the labyrinth is Solitude,
足の臭い消しはメンソール
menthol is for getting rid of foot odor.
終わり終わりそろそろ終わり
It's ending, ending, ending soon.
こんな長い歌詞は嫌だ
I hate lyrics this long.
ギャラに合わない疲れる仕事
This tiring job doesn't match the pay.
中身の人とプラン考えて
Think of a plan with the person inside.
違う違う本当は違う
No, no, that's not true.
ここは二次元で三次元
This is 2D and 3D.
表表表が表で
Front, front, the front is the front,
歴史浅いでまだ超力
history is shallow, yet still super powerful.
記録塗り替えたら作る
If records are rewritten, we'll create.
はーい！
Hi!
はい、ということで始まりましたー！
All right, and so it begins!
一発目から疲れる楽曲だったね、本当に。
That was a really exhausting song for the first one.
本日ですけども、ホロライブゲーマーズ結成記念ライブ2024ということで、
Today is the Hololive Gamers Formation Anniversary Live 2024,
ハッシュタグがございます。
and we have a hashtag.
#ホロゲマズ結成記念LIVE2024
ポストいっぱいしてください！
Please post a lot!
今回のステージなんですけど、みんな、後ろのこのビコビコさ、気づいた？
About this stage, everyone, did you notice the flickering in the back?
我々の声でビコビコ動くらしくて、
It seems to move in sync with our voices,
ちょっと、ころねやってみようか。
so let's have Korone try it out.
わあーー！！
Waaa!!
すごい！ビコビコしております。
Amazing! It's flickering away.
後ろも見て、「げまずえでぃしょん!!!!」
Look behind us, it says "Gamers Edition!!!!"
オープニングも可愛かったね。
The opening was cute too.
このロゴね。
This logo.
みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for coming!
今日誕生日の人、おめでとう！
Happy birthday to anyone celebrating today!
今回は結成記念ライブということで、説明お願いします。
Since this is a formation anniversary live, please explain.
そうだね、お願いしますミオさん。
That's right, please go ahead Mio-san.
ホロライブゲーマーズは、みんなが同じような時期にデビューしたのではなくてですね、
Hololive Gamers didn't all debut at the same time.
フブキが6月に1期生としてデビュー。
Fubuki debuted in June as a 1st Gen member.
その後に、うちが12月に、フブキと一緒にホロライブゲーマーズとして、
Then, in December, I debuted with Fubuki as Hololive Gamers,
最初二人で、うちだけソロデビュー。
starting as a duo, with just my solo debut.
その後に4月に、おかころがデビューして、
After that, in April, OkaKoro debuted,
今の4人の形になったということで。
leading to our current four-member lineup.
ま、一応発足の12月を、結成記念とさせていただいたということで。
So, we've set December, the month of our launch, as our formation anniversary.
聞いてなかったでしょ！
You weren't listening, were you!
聞いてた！
We were!
12月にミオしゃが来たから、それで結成して、それの記念ライブだよって話ね。
You said since Mio-sha arrived in December, we formed then, and this is the anniversary live for it.
聞いてる聞いてる！
We're listening, we're listening!
このあともまだまだ歌うのでな、
We'll still be singing plenty more after this,
ちょっと体力大丈夫そう？
so is your stamina holding up?
もうバテてきたよ。
I'm already worn out.
早い早い！
Too early!
（抱き合う二人）
(The two hugging)
あ、回復して、回復して。
Ah, heal me, heal me.
回復した？
Did you heal?
めっちゃ疲れた。
I'm so tired.
なんでだよ！
Why?!
ひしぐられている。
You're being squished.
ドキドキしたよね。そしてドキドキと言えども...
It was exciting, wasn't it? And speaking of excitement...
さてということで、今回なんですけども、なんとコンセプトを決めておりまして、我々。
Well, for this time, we have actually decided on a concept.
はい！
Yes!
メンバーの歌ってほしい曲をあみだくじで決めて、
We used an Amidakuji to decide which songs we wanted members to sing,
それぞれがプロデュースした楽曲を歌ってもらうという。
and each member will sing a song produced by another.
はい。
Yes.
プロデュース形式のライブとなっております。
It's a producer-style live performance.
すごーい、面白い！
Amazing, how interesting!
今回ね、あの、誰がどの曲をやるかとか話し合わずにですね、
This time, without discussing who would do which song,
突然あみだくじを用意しまして。
we suddenly prepared an Amidakuji lottery.
そう。
Right.
「じゃ、どうぞあみだがいいから引いてね」みたいな感じで、うちがあみだくじで決めさせていただきました。
Like, "Go ahead and pick a line," and I had the Amidakuji decide.
そうそう。用意してくれたの。ねー。
Right, right. She prepared it for us. Yeah.
ということで、まずは1曲目は！
So, for the first song...!
ドゥルルルルル...
Durururururu...
誰だ？
Who is it?
はい！おかゆーー！
Yes! It's Okayu!
疲れてるって言ったけど大丈夫、おかゆ？
You said you were tired, are you okay, Okayu?
でもね...
But you know...
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
だって、この曲はね、僕の大好きな妹が選んでくれたわけですからね。
Because, you see, this song was chosen by my beloved younger sister.
妹じゃねーだよな。
I'm not your younger sister, though.
おかしい。白上さんがプロデュースしていただきました！
How strange. Shirakami-san produced this for her!
嬉しい〜。
I'm so happy.
どんな思いでちょっと選んだのか聞きたい。
I want to hear a bit about your thoughts behind choosing it.
いや、これおかゆに、この楽曲を聴いた時にまずおかゆに歌ってほしいなって思った楽曲で。
Well, when I heard this song, the first person I wanted to hear sing it was Okayu.
ずっと思っていて、で今回のこのライブやるってので、お、これちょうどいい、おかゆに歌ってもらうっていう。
I'd been thinking that for a while, and when this live came up, I thought, "Oh, this is perfect, let's have Okayu sing it."
いや、歌詞がね、すごいおかゆっぽいんだよ。
No, really, the lyrics are so very Okayu-like.
え、そうなの？
Eh, is that so?
楽しみに。
Look forward to it.
可愛い楽曲となっておりますので、じゃあみんな準備しますか？
It's a very cute song, so shall we all get ready?
よしよし、行くぞ行くぞ。おかゆ頑張れー。
Alright, let's go, let's go. Good luck, Okayu!
ありえない幻想
An impossible fantasy
あふれだす妄想
Overflowing delusions
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
息をするように嘘ついて もう
Telling lies as naturally as breathing already
あたしやっぱりいらない子？
Am I really an unwanted child after all?
こぼれ出しちゃった承認欲求
My need for approval has spilled over
もっとココロ満たしてよ
Fill my heart even more
アスパルテーム 甘い夢
Aspartame, a sweet dream
あたしだけに愛をください
Please give your love only to me
重乗り マジ盛り 恋して 愛して 救済 執行
Over-ride, serious-mode, fall in love, love me, salvation, execution
ねー、好きって言ってよ？
Hey, say you love me?
ありえない幻想
An impossible fantasy
あふれだす妄想
Overflowing delusions
とまんない つまんない 欲が散らばって
Unstoppable, boring, desires are scattered
求めてる愛情
The love I seek
隠してる烈情
The lust I hide
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
誰のこと見てんの？
Who are you looking at?
こういうの好きなの？
Do you like this kind of thing?
DDとかガチでやめてください
Seriously, stop being a DD
可愛くなりたい！
I want to become cute!
キラキラしたい！
I want to sparkle!
もっともっとガチで褒めてください
Please praise me more and more, seriously
泣いちゃう惨憺
I'll cry miserably
開けちゃうシャンパン
I'll open the champagne
今夜も配信見てくれるよね？
You'll watch the stream tonight too, right?
ね？
Right?
独占させてよ
Let me monopolize you
本音なんでしょ？
It's your true feelings, isn't it?
もっともっとガチで推してください
Please support me more and more, seriously
飲み過ぎ注意 オーバードーズ
Be careful of drinking too much, overdose
クラクラさせていつだって
Make me dizzy, always
重乗り マジ盛り アガって サガって 救済 執行
Over-ride, serious-mode, going up, going down, salvation, execution
ねー、好きって言わせて？
Hey, let me say I love you?
噛みついた衝動
The impulse I bit into
戻れない焦燥
The impatience I can't return from
たまんない みんな指が絡まって
Unbearable, everyone's fingers are intertwined
ときめいた表情
A heart-pounding expression
何も言わないで
Don't say anything
君だけがきっど王子様
Only you are surely my prince
ありえない幻想
An impossible fantasy
あふれだす妄想
Overflowing delusions
とまんない つまんない 欲が散らばって
Unstoppable, boring, desires are scattered
求めてる愛情
The love I seek
隠してる烈情
The lust I hide
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
あたしだけずっと追いかけて
Just keep chasing only me forever
ねー
Hey
もう待てないの
I can't wait anymore
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
はい、『妄想アスパルテーム』歌わせていただきました！
Yes, I sang 'Mousou Aspartame'!
おかゆ〜！ミオしゃだよ！すごい可愛かったよ！
Okayu~! It's Miosha! You were so cute!
ほんと？いや、なんかあまりさ、こんな可愛い曲歌うことないからさ。
Really? Well, you know, I don't usually sing such cute songs.
いや、もううちこのおかゆの衣装めっちゃ好きでさ。
No, I really love this outfit of Okayu's.
え、ほんと？嬉しい。
Eh, really? I'm happy.
このスカートとかすごい好き好きだけど、ふわふわ。
I really love this skirt and all, it's so fluffy.
本当だ。かわいい。
It's true. So cute.
本当によかった。
I'm really glad.
なんかさ、色々いるよ。
Hey, there's all sorts of things here.
もしもし、あの、今は気にしないで。
Hello, um, don't mind them for now.
え？
Eh?
いいからいいから。
It's fine, it's fine.
そうなんだ。わかった。
Oh, okay. I see.
いや本当さ、この曲もめっちゃ、おかゆにめっちゃ合ってる感じしたけど、
Seriously, I felt like this song really suited Okayu perfectly,
どうだった？この曲歌ってみて。
how was it? Singing this song.
まあ確かに歌いやすかったけど、
Well, it was certainly easy to sing, but
フブキPが僕のことをよく見てくれてるからこういう風なことできるんだなと思って、
I thought it's because Fubuki-P watches me closely that she can do things like this,
あれ？
Wait?
ああ！なんか、この頭の中にころさんいる気がちょっと...
Ah! I have a feeling Korone-san is inside this head...
違う違う違う！もう、これあの、
No, no, no! This is, um,
あれ？抱き枕じゃないから。
Wait? It's not a body pillow.
あ、そう？
Oh, really?
違うよ。
No.
なんか、ころさんの匂いしたような気がしたんだけど。
I thought I caught a whiff of Korone-san's scent.
しないしないしない、全然、全然しないから。
It doesn't, it doesn't, not at all, not at all.
わかった。
Okay.
そう。無視して、無視無視。
Right. Ignore them, just ignore.
はい。うん。
Yes. Yeah.
まあ、でも良かったね、すごい。
Well, but it was great, really.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
嬉しいね、この曲選んでもらえて。
I'm happy that you chose this song.
次はさ、ミオちゃんの番でしょ！
Next is Mio-chan's turn!
わあ、ちょっと緊張しちゃうな、頑張ってくるよ。
Wow, I'm getting a bit nervous, I'll do my best.
僕がね、ミオちゃんに歌ってほしい歌をプロデュースしました！
I produced the song I want Mio-chan to sing!
プロデュースしてもらいました！
I had it produced!
それこそミオちゃんも歌うとめちゃめちゃカッコいい系のこと多いから。
Since Mio-chan often does really cool things when she sings.
そうだね、どちらかというとそうかも。
That's true, maybe more so.
今回は、ミオファのみんなにめっちゃ可愛いミオちゃんをお届けしたくて、
This time, I wanted to deliver a super cute Mio-chan to all the Mio-fa,
かなりアイドルミオを楽しんでいただけると思います。
so I think you'll be able to enjoy a very "Idol Mio."
そうだね、はい！
That's right, yes!
アイドルミオ、頑張っちゃうよ！
Idol Mio, I'll do my best!
可愛い、もう可愛い、すでに。
Cute, already cute.
ちょっと、情報量すごいけどね、やっぱり。
Though the amount of info is crazy, as expected.
無視しきれないんだけど。
I can't fully ignore it.
まあまあまあ...
Well, well...
何やってんだおい、おいおい、いい加減にしろよ。
What are you doing, hey, come on, cut it out.
怒られてる。
They're getting scolded.
はい、じゃあ、もう、行っちゃう？ちょっと緊張してきたけど。
Alright, then, shall we go? I'm getting a bit nervous.
わかった。
Okay.
ミオちゃんの心の準備ができてたら、ちょっと準備しに行きましょう。
If Mio-chan is mentally ready, let's go get ready.
はい！じゃあ、頑張って歌います！
Yes! Then, I'll do my best singing!
はい、頑張ってね！
Yes, good luck!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
もう一回 こっち向いて
Look this way one more time
言いたいことがもっとあるから
Because I have more things I want to say
もう一回 こっち向いて
Look this way one more time
本気が揺れる 愛のFuture
Earnestness wavers, Love's Future
だから こっち向いて
So look this way
まわれ地球 恋をのせて
Rotate, Earth, carrying love
だから こっち向いて
So look this way
偶然じゃない Fanta Future!
It's not a coincidence, Fanta Future!
Fantastic future 作詞：畑亜貴 作曲：太田雅友
Fantastic future - Lyrics: Aki Hata, Composition: Masatomo Ota
私から誘う勇気を
Give me the courage to invite you
くださいと月に願うの
I wish to the moon
切ない心に魔法をかけてみましょう
Let's cast a spell on this painful heart
未来への近道ね
It's a shortcut to the future
甘くなれ 笑顔で
Become sweet, with a smile
君をとろけちゃえ
Melt you away
今日の夜空を見つめ
Gazing at today's night sky
ちょっと背伸びして
Standing a bit on tip-toes
もう一回 こっち向いて
Look this way one more time
言いたいことがもっとあるから
Because I have more things I want to say
もう一回 こっち向いて
Look this way one more time
本気が揺れる 愛のFuture
Earnestness wavers, Love's Future
だから こっち向いて
So look this way
まわれ地球 恋をのせて
Rotate, Earth, carrying love
だから こっち向いて
So look this way
偶然じゃない Fanta Future!
It's not a coincidence, Fanta Future!
私だけ好きになってと
Saying "Like only me"
大それた望み持ってる
I have such a bold wish
捨てちゃいけない 魔法がゆっくり効いて
I shouldn't throw it away, the magic is slowly taking effect
未来では仲良しね
In the future, we'll be close
軽くなれ 身体は
Become light, my body
君とふわふわ
Fluffy with you
今日の夜空を飛んで
Flying through today's night sky
遠い場所へと
To a distant place
ねえずっと 会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you
恋することが世界の平和
Loving someone is world peace
ねえずっと 会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you
変えてみせる 愛でFuture
I'll show you I can change it, with love's Future
大好き 会いたかった
I love you, I wanted to see you
まわる地球 恋する純情
The rotating Earth, love's pure heart
大好き 会いたかった 何でもできる Fantastic future
I love you, I wanted to see you, I can do anything, Fantastic future
切ない心に魔法をかけたら
If I cast a spell on my painful heart
二人で
The two of us
遠い場所へと
to a far-off place
ねえずっと会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you
恋することが世界の平和
Falling in love is world peace
ねえずっと会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you
変えてみせるよ 愛で Future
I'll show you I can change it with love, Future
大好き 会いたかった
I love you, I wanted to see you
まわる地球 恋する順序
The spinning Earth, the order of falling in love
大好き 会いたかった
I love you, I wanted to see you
何でもできる Fantastic future
I can do anything, Fantastic future
はい！どうでしたでしょうか
Hi! How was that?
Fantastic future!
よかったー！
It was great!
ありがとう！耳、すっごい聞いてる
Thank you! My ears were really listening.
よかったよー、ミオしゃ可愛かったー！
It was good! Mio-sha was so cute!
ありがとうありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
こねも衣装変わってるね！
Kone, your outfit has changed too!
ちょっと変えてみたの！
I tried changing it a bit!
おー！
Oh!
この衣装めっちゃ可愛いんだよな！
This outfit is really cute!
こねの衣装はまだいいの！
Never mind my outfit for now!
ミオしゃの歌をね！
Let's talk about your song!
ちょっと感想聞かせてよ、どうだった？歌ってみて
Tell me what you thought. How was it, singing it?
えーと、うちはこの曲初めて歌ったんだけど
Well, it was my first time singing this song...
なんかね、意外と歌いやすかった！
and it was surprisingly easy to sing!
おかゆは分かってんだな、って
I thought, "Okayu really knows me."
確かにおかゆがね、プロデュースしたからね
True, since Okayu produced it.
そうそうそう
Right, right, right.
よかった
That's good.
部下二人もなんか言ってる？
Are the two subordinates saying something?
あ？
Huh?
え、そうなの？なに？
Oh, really? What?
なんか、ホロゲマズ結成記念ライブ2024が
It seems HoloGamers Anniversary Live 2024...
なんと、Xのトレンド1位になったそうです！
...has actually reached #1 on X trends!
やったー！
Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんながいっぱい呟いてくれて
Everyone's been tweeting so much,
嬉しいー
I'm so happy!
ありがとうねー
Thank you all!
今日は敵が少なかったのかな？
Maybe there weren't many enemies today?
敵って言うなよ！
Don't call them enemies!
Xで共に戦う仲間だろ
They're comrades fighting together on X!
確かに
True.
やめろよ
Stop it. (lol)
嬉しいね、なんかね
It's really nice.
そうだね
Yeah.
次のね、こねの曲は
Kone, for your next song...
うちがプロデュースしました！
...I produced it!
あのね、すごーく難しかった！
You know, it was very difficult!
あ、難しかった？
Oh, was it hard?
めちゃめちゃ難しかったよ！いっぱい練習したの
It was super hard! I practiced a lot.
だから、不安
So, I'm nervous.
うちさ、好きな曲なんだけど
It's a song I like, but...
うち自分では多分歌えないなって思って
I thought I probably couldn't sing it myself.
もうね、これってなって
So I decided, "This is the one!"
めちゃめちゃ練習しました、今日のために
I practiced so much for today.
嬉しいな。絶対こねの声には合うと思って選んだから
I'm glad. I chose it because I thought it would definitely suit your voice.
ちょっとリスナーさん、聴いててね
Everyone, please listen.
楽しみにしててね
Look forward to it!
じゃあこね、頑張って。うちちょっと行ってくるから
Then, good luck, Kone. I'm going to head off for a bit.
頑張る
I'll do my best.
わかった
Okay.
行ってくる、帰るから
I'm going. I'll be back.
これ持って帰ってちゃんと
Take this back with you properly.
あ、そうだね。みんな行くよ、早く
Oh, right. Let's go everyone, quickly!
いいの、いいのもう
It's fine, it's fine already.
散々自由にさせたでしょ、もう帰るよ
I've let you be free enough, we're going back now.
声出すな
Don't make a sound.
帰るぞ
We're leaving.
頑張ってねー！
Good luck!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
この混沌とした令和のインターネットを照らす一筋の光
A single ray of light that illuminates this chaotic Reiwa Internet
電子の海を漂うオタクに笑顔を
Bringing smiles to the otaku drifting in the electronic sea
未来の平和をお約束
Promising peace for the future
躁鬱だけどまかせとけ
I'm manic-depressive, but leave it to me
インターネットエンジェル、ただいま降臨！
Internet Angel, descending now!
社会をやめろ
Quit society
家族をやめろ
Quit family
人間関係をやめろ
Quit human relationships
今すぐ薄暗い部屋で、青白いライトを浴びろ
Right now, in a dim room, bask in the pale light
大丈夫、怖かったこと全部上書きするからね
It's okay, I'll overwrite everything you were afraid of
現実よりも Crazy for you
Even more than reality, I'm Crazy for you
おかしくなりそう
I feel like I'm going crazy
オンなほど情報過多のインターネット
The more turned on, the more information-overloaded is the Internet
今すぐ助けてあげるよ
I'll save you right now
よだーりん だーりん
Yo-Darling Darling
ウソはウソであると見抜ける
Lies can be seen as lies
この愛は暴走しちゃうし
This love is going out of control
壊れてしまうけど
And it will break, but...
考えなくていいんだよ
You don't have to think
もうすぐ楽になるから
Because it will soon be easier
脳内に乱反射する
Diffusely reflecting in my brain
POISON RADIO
麻薬より甘いよ
It's sweeter than drugs
いいね　よくないね
Like, not good
キミにとっては毒だね
It's poison for you
いいね　よくないね
Like, not good
それでも飲むんだね
But you still drink it
いいね　よくないね
Like, not good
二人の秘密だね
It's a secret between us
私だけ見ててね
Look only at me
まるで天使のように微笑む
Smiling just like an angel
強めの幻覚 インターネット
Strong hallucinations, internet
そして悪魔みたいにささやく
And whispering like a devil
アナタだけのデパパスィ
Your very own depapasity
浅い眠りと承認欲求のオーバードーズ
Shallow sleep and an overdose of the desire for recognition
脳天直撃する私たちだけの宗教と光
A religion and light only for us that hits the crown of the head
倫理より激しく生きた宇宙すら侵食する恋
A love that lived more intensely than ethics, eroding even the universe
何度も送られる毒電波を優しさだけで包んで
Wrapping the poison radio waves sent over and over in only kindness
逆さまのコンピューターと断片的なカウンセリング
An upside-down computer and fragmentary counseling
きらめく屋上で奏でた夢見心地の旋律
A dreamy melody played on a sparkling rooftop
夕暮れ時にさよならの練習をして
Practicing saying goodbye at twilight
壊して愛して許して狂って狂って甘く狂わせて
Break me, love me, forgive me, go crazy, go crazy, make me sweetly crazy
ゆらぎ始める世界
The world begins to sway
曖昧になる風景
The scenery becomes ambiguous
アナタだけが映っているメモリー
A memory where only you are reflected
神様なんていないよ
There is no such thing as God
このふざけたインターネットは七色のサイケデリック
This foolish internet is a seven-colored psychedelic
SNSという瓶詰め地獄に救済を
Salvation for the bottled hell called SNS
過去の歴史は見ないふり アナタもカメラのこちら側に
Pretending not to see past history, you too on this side of the camera
インターネット・エンジェル かわいく参上
Internet Angel, making a cute appearance
まるで天使のように抱きつく
Clinging just like an angel
強めの幻覚 インターネット
Strong hallucinations, internet
そして悪魔みたいにキスする
And kissing like a devil
アナタだけのニヒリズム
Your very own nihilism
どうでしたかー！
How was it?!
うわああ！すごかったよー！
Waaaa! It was amazing!
げまずでふれんどー！！！
Gamers de Friend!!!
似合うね。
It suits you.
めっちゃ頑張ってたね、すごかった！
You were working so hard, it was amazing!
ありがとうー。おる？
Thank you. Is someone there?
動いてるね。
They're moving.
あとちょっとね。
Just a little more.
フブちゃんも。
Fubuki-chan too.
そう。かわいい。
Yes. Cute.
次の曲はこの制服で踊ります。
I'll dance the next song in this uniform.
はー。
Hah.
次の曲はね。
The next song is...
こね、フブちゃん、あ、ころねが選んだんだけど。
This, Fubuki-chan, ah, Korone chose it but...
そうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
この可愛いキュートボイスでね、ロックンロールしてほしいの。
I want you to rock 'n' roll with this cute voice.
まさかすぎる選曲でちょっとびっくりしたけど。
I was a bit surprised by the unexpected choice.
でもらしいっちゃらしかったよね。
But it was very "us", wasn't it?
ロックンロール！
Rock 'n' roll!
ロックンロールな感じの曲を歌いますけども。
We're going to sing a rock 'n' roll-ish song.
やるぜ。
Let's do it.
ホロライブらしい曲だったな、選曲やっぱ間違ってなかったね。
It was a very Hololive-like song, the choice wasn't wrong after all.
なんかいる、なんか怖い。
Something's there, it's a bit scary.
ちょっと吐息、吐息がやばい。
The breathing, the breathing is crazy.
ちょっと、ね、近い。
Wait, it's close.
近い、近い、やめて。
Close, close, stop it.
やめて、あっち行って。
Stop it, go over there.
泣かないで、泣くな。
Don't cry, don't cry.
こっちこっち、あっちあっちほら。
This way, that way, look.
あんたたち「ころねすき」って名前なんだよ。
Your names are "Korone-suki".
何をしてるんだ、泣くな。
What are you doing? Don't cry.
ほら、え？
Look, eh?
やだ。え？あ、やだ。え？
No. Eh? Ah, no. Eh?
ANGEL...
恥ずかしい、こんなところで。
How embarrassing, in a place like this.
やだ！え、あれ？
No! Eh, wait?
あ！
Ah!
なんてことだ。
Oh my goodness.
なんか悪魔みたいにキスしてる。
It's like they're kissing like devils.
やだ、ねえ、きもい。
No, hey, it's gross.
激しいんだけど。
It's intense.
何、ちょっと待って。
What, wait a second.
クリスマスの前にそんなことしないで、ころねすき同士で。
Don't do that before Christmas, you Korone-suki fellows.
やだ。
No.
帰りなさい、早く。
Go home, quickly.
帰っちゃうんだね。
They're going home.
何だったんだよ、それはよ。
What was that all about?!
じゃあね、ころねもじゃあ。
Well then, Korone too.
あっち行くぞ。
Let's go over there.
フブちゃん！
Fubuki-chan!
はい！
Yes!
頑張ろうね！
Let's do our best!
ありがとうねー！
Thank you!
いやあ、恐ろしいもの見たね。
Phew, we saw something terrifying.
Let's go!
喉からヒップへ 真っ赤に飛び散る ファンクなウイルス みたいなおまえ
From throat to hip, scattering in bright red, like a funky virus, you are
暴走ボディーで キュートな誘惑 世界にはびこる ウソをこわせ
With a runaway body, cute temptation, break the lies spreading through the world
世紀末だって つぎはぎな夢さ
Even the end of the century is a patchwork dream
恋の出口なきゃ 死ねるわけないだろ
If there's no exit for love, there's no way I can die
容姿は幼稚で 陽気なようでも 酔うと異様に ヨエナナイツ
Even if your appearance is childish and cheerful, when you're drunk, it's a strangely YOENA nights
ロリータ・ウィンクで キャンディーなぶって 娼婦の唇で しゃぶってみろよ
With a Lolita wink, licking a candy, try sucking it with a prostitute's lips
世紀末だって つぎはぎな夢さ
Even the end of the century is a patchwork dream
愛に追いつきゃ 悲しみも消える
If you catch up with love, sadness will also disappear
世紀末だって 遊びの欠けらさ
Even the end of the century is a fragment of play
キッスばらまいて 未来へ行こうぜ
Scatter kisses and let's go to the future
Don't let me down My sweet baby BAMBINA
抱きしめた あの夜は 秘密さ
The night we held each other is a secret
ヌードになったら 天使の羽根が
When you become nude, your angel wings...
バレるぜ BAMBINA Let's go!
...will be revealed, BAMBINA. Let's go!
BAMBINA BAMBINA I love you
キングのルールも ギャングのコードも 今夜のダンスは 止められないさ
Neither the king's rule nor the gang's code can stop tonight's dance
BAMBINA BAMBINA I love you
ハートのジッパー こっそり開けたら 立体ビジョンの 弓形ビーナス
If you secretly open the zipper of your heart, a 3D vision of a bow-shaped Venus
BAMBINA BAMBINA I love you
世紀末だって つぎはぎな夢さ
Even the end of the century is a patchwork dream
愛に追いつきゃ 悲しみも消える
If you catch up with love, sadness will also disappear
世紀末だって 遊びの欠けらさ
Even the end of the century is a fragment of play
キッスばらまいて 未来へ行こうぜ
Scatter kisses and let's go to the future
Don't let me down My sweet baby BAMBINA
鳥カゴに 閉じ込めて 会いたい
I want to lock you in a birdcage and see you
退屈すると ちゃんと浮気する
When I get bored, I'll definitely cheat
小悪魔 BAMBINA Don't let me down
Little devil BAMBINA. Don't let me down
My sweet baby BAMBINA
抱きしめた あの夜は 秘密さ
The night we held each other is a secret
ヌードになったら 天使だったね
When you became nude, you were an angel
魅惑の BAMBINA!
Enchanting BAMBINA!
BAMBINA BAMBINA I love you
はーい！ということで、ばみーだれでしたー！ありがとうございましたー！
Hi! And so, that was Bamidare! Thank you very much!
わっ！えっ！ああー！
Wah! Eh! Ahhh!
あららー、ちょっとなんか…ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って。
Oh dear, wait a second... wait, wait.
あららー、ちょっとなんか、前に並んで、前に並んで。
Oh dear, look at this... okay, line up in front, line up.
誰が誰？
Who's who?
アイ・ラブ・ユー。
I love you.
あ、痛っ！あ、こけちゃった、ごめん。
Ah, ouch! Oh, I fell over, sorry.
ほら、これ、さっきから… おパンツじゃねえ、おかゆだろお前！
Look at this, ever since... It's not "panty", you're Okayu, right?!
えー？ほら、今斜め前向いてるのは誰？あなたは？
Eh? Look, who's the one facing diagonally forward now? Who are you?
あこねだよー、あこねだ。あこねだよ。
I'm Akone~, it's Akone. I'm Akone.
こね、なんか今強気みたいな声しましたけど、あ、怒れる、怒れる。むってして、むって。
Kone, you sounded a bit confident just now... oh, she's getting angry. Make a pouting face, pout.
うぐー。あははは。
Uguu. Ahahaha.
で、なんかわーわー言ってるのがいるんだけど、これはもしやミオ？
And there's someone making a fuss... could this be Mio?
うーち、うーち。うちだよー。
Uchi, uchi. It's me~
あ、なんかこんなんなっちゃった。かわいい。かわいー。
Ah, look what happened. So cute. So cute.
かわいい、かわいいねー。よしよしよし。
Cute, you're so cute. There, there.
あーでも、戻ってきなさいあなたたち全く！さっきからずっと変なポーズ見てるでしょ、バカ野郎。
Ah, but come back here already, you guys! We've been looking at your weird poses for ages, you dummies.
戻れ戻れ！絶景じゃないんだよ。ほら、元の位置に戻ってきなさい。
Go back, go back! It's not a "great view". Come on, get back to your original spots.
ほらほら、あっち行け、あっち。全く。ちゃんと着替えてくるんだよ。
Come on, go over there, over there. Honestly. Go change back properly.
ちゃんと解除スイッチあるから、解除スイッチ。全く。
There's a release switch, use the release switch. Honestly.
もうー、そろそろ戻った？大丈夫？…まだ？
Geez... have you returned yet? Are you okay? ...Still?
まだー！いつまで着替えてんだよ！
Not yet! How long are you going to take to change?!
戻ったよー！よかったよかった。見えなくなってる。
We're back! Thank goodness. I can't see anything.
いいんだよそれで。何言ってんだよ。
That's fine. What are you talking about?
おかゆ、そういうときはな、
Okayu, in times like that...
こうするんだよ！やばいやばい！やばいよ！やめなさい！
You do this! Whoa, whoa! That's bad! Stop it!
一気にちっちゃい人たちになっちゃって。
You all suddenly became tiny people.
ちっちゃい、ちっちゃい体どうだった、みんな？楽しかったー！
How was the tiny body, everyone? It was fun!
ほんとに。動きづらくなかった？いや、かわいかった。
Really. Wasn't it hard to move? No, it was cute.
可愛がられるってあんなに幸せなことなんだね。元からかわいいだろ。
Being doted on is such a happy thing, isn't it? You're cute to begin with.
ふふふのふ。おいおいおい。
Hehehe. Hey, hey, hey.
ということでね、一通りで、我々プロデュースした楽曲が終わりましたけども。
And so, the songs we produced have all finished for now, but...
まだまだ歌えますよね？このあともね。歌いましょう！
We can still sing more, right? After this as well. Let's sing!
次は、なんと、デュエットということで！
Next is, surprisingly, a duet!
おー！どの組み合わせだろう？誰と誰と歌うのかな？
Oh! Which combination will it be? Who's singing with who?
誰かなー、誰かなー、誰とかなー？
Who could it be~?
怖い、怖い、その動き見たから。こわいよ、だめだよ。
Scary, scary, I saw those moves. It's scary, stop it.
いいよ、こわいよ。誰との壁？
It's okay. It's scary. A wall with who?
やろうか、こっちも、こうやって。えいっ！
Shall we do it too? Like this. Hiyah!
え、これの意味、意味あんの？インベーダー？
Eh, does this have any meaning? Invader?
インベーダーってことかな？ということで、次のデュエットの準備をしに、皆さん行くぞ！
Maybe it means Invaders? So, let's go get ready for the next duet, everyone!
おー！行け行け行け！楽しみー！
Oh! Let's go, let's go! I'm looking forward to it!
レッツゴー！よいしょ、よいしょ。
Let's go! Heave-ho, heave-ho.
るるる...
Ru ru ru...
あー、恋の定義がわかんない
Ah, I don't get the definition of love
まず好きって基準もわかんない
First, I don't even get the criteria for "liking"
要は、恋してるときが恋らしい。客観？主観？エビデンスプリーズ！
Basically, when you're in love, that's love. Objective? Subjective? Evidence, please!
愛は計算じゃ解けない
Love can't be solved with calculations
まず普通の計算も解けない
First, I can't even solve normal calculations
要は、そんな状態が愛らしい。アイノウ？ユーノウ？もう大抵の
Basically, that state is adorable. I know? You know? Most of...
事象において Qがあって Aを出して解けるのに
In most phenomena, there's a Q and an A, and they can be solved
間違って、間違って、解のないこの気持ちはなんだろう
But I'm wrong, I'm wrong, what is this feeling with no solution?
検証 is 不明
Verification is... unknown
DAZING!! モーションは相対性にステイ
DAZING!! Motion stays in relativity
チューリングラブ 見つめあったって解けないメロウ
Turing Love. Even if we gaze at each other, it's an unsolvable mellow
ワッツイズラブ いま123で証そうか。言葉で生み出すクエスチョン...シンプル Q.E.D.
What is love? Shall we prove it now with a 1, 2, 3? A question created by words... simple Q.E.D.
今日こそ証明しよう！目に見えないしよう！無理難題
Let's prove it today! Let's make the invisible... an impossible challenge!
1234 導き出したい たどり着きたい 最適解へ
1, 2, 3, 4. I want to derive it, I want to reach the optimal solution
何回回ったってぶつかっちゃったって
No matter how many times we go around or bump into each other
不可思議なこのアノマリー 解き明かす過程さえ必要条件です
This strange anomaly, even the process of solving it is a necessary condition
3次元(立体)における2点AB間の距離を求めよ。
Calculate the distance between two points A and B in 3D (solid) space.
的な感じだと思ってたのに
I thought it was something like that...
座標も公式も見当たらないし
But I can't find coordinates or formulas
参考資料にも載っていないから 君と生み出してみたいじゃん
And it's not in the reference materials, so I want to create it with you
3次元(世界)におけるこの気持ちの求め方
The way to calculate this feeling in the 3D (world)
○だって×だって不安にとってイコールで
A circle or a cross, for anxiety, they are equal
近くなって遠くなって揺れるこの気持ちの針も
Becoming closer then further, the needle of these swaying feelings too
条件 is 明瞭 Steppin'!!
Condition is clear. Steppin'!!
ちょーわそー　あいしょうミステイク
Harmony, compatibility mistake.
チューリングラブ　騒ぎ出した胸の痛くなるほど
Turing love, my heart starts to pound so much it hurts.
証明はいまも確度を増しているようだ
The proof seems to be gaining more accuracy even now.
曖昧も除外して
Exclude all ambiguity,
最大の仮説を
and take the greatest hypothesis...
いまふたりなら　実証できそう
If it's the two of us now, we might be able to prove it.
チューリングラブ　見つめあったってキリないメロウ
Turing love, an endless mellow even if we gaze at each other.
ワンステップいまは123で上がったって
One step, even if we went up with 123 now.
言葉で生み出すパッション
The passion created by words.
ハートで高鳴るアンサー
The answer pounding in the heart.
測ったって不確定性　ぼくらのBPM
Even if measured, it's uncertainty, our BPM.
チューリングラブ　宙に舞ったって三世の因果も
Turing love, even the karma of three lifetimes flying in the air...
フォーリンラブ　いまはXYZまで解りそうさ
Fallin' love, now it seems we can understand even XYZ.
確かめさせてピタゴラス
Let me confirm it, Pythagoras.
確かめさせて今
Let me confirm it now.
予測済み可塑性　いま触れてみる
Predicted plasticity, I'll try to touch it now.
さあ証明しよう
Now let's prove it,
間違いのないように
so there's no mistake.
証明しよう
Let's prove it.
この感情全部全部
All of these feelings, all of them.
証明しよう
Let's prove it.
正解があるなら
If there is a correct answer.
証明しよう
Let's prove it.
推測を超えて
Beyond speculation.
証明しよう
Let's prove it,
間違いのないように
so there's no mistake.
証明しよう
Let's prove it.
この感情全部全部
All of these feelings, all of them.
証明しよう
Let's prove it.
正解があるなら
If there is a correct answer.
証明しよう
Let's prove it.
シンプルなQ.E.D.
A simple Q.E.D.
L R L R STOP & Dash & UP & TALK B B A B S (t)art
L R L R STOP & Dash & UP & TALK B B A B S
L R
STOP
UP
TALK
L R
Dash
リモコン
Remocon
これが私リモートで
This is the machine
コントロールする機械です
I control remotely.
少し歪な形しておりますが、
It has a slightly warped shape,
使えます。
but it works.
UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A 右左
Up side down A B A B B A B A Right Left.
L R L R STOP & Dash & UP & TALK 異常ナシ
L R L R STOP & Dash & UP & TALK No abnormalities.
もうちょっとで外に出られるのにな
I'm almost able to go outside though.
どうやってもうまくいかねぇ
No matter what I do, it doesn't go well.
まだまだ足りない
Still not enough.
座る 座る oh SIT DOWN PLEASE YEAH!
Sit down, sit down, oh SIT DOWN PLEASE YEAH!
フィードバックに体預けて
Entrust your body to the feedback.
廻る 廻る oh TURN IT AROUND YEAH!
Turn around, turn around, oh TURN IT AROUND YEAH!
唸りをあげてモーター状態
Cranking it up, motor state.
踊る 踊る oh DANCIN' NIGHT YEAH!
Dance, dance, oh DANCIN' NIGHT YEAH!
マッシュアップでもれなくアガる。
Rising up without fail with a mash-up.
声をあげて oh SINGIN' NOW YEAH!
Raise your voice, oh SINGIN' NOW YEAH!
あの子よりもうまく歌いたい。
I want to sing better than that girl.
これが僕リモートで
This is the machine
操縦できる機械です。
I can pilot remotely.
説明書は紛失しておりますが
The manual is lost,
使えます。
but it works.
UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A 右左
Up side down A B A B B A B A Right Left.
L R L R STOP & Dash & UP & TALK 異常ナシ
L R L R STOP & Dash & UP & TALK No abnormalities.
からかってるみたいないつもの顔
That usual face that looks like it's teasing.
余裕でしょ？
You're cool, right?
今日はかなり本気だぜ？
I'm pretty serious today, you know?
ほら すぐキメるぜ
Look, I'll finish it soon.
座る 座る oh SIT DOWN PLEASE YEAH!
Sit down, sit down, oh SIT DOWN PLEASE YEAH!
トークバックを頭に挿して
Plug the talkback into your head.
廻る 廻る oh TURN IT AROUND YEAH!
Turn around, turn around, oh TURN IT AROUND YEAH!
ちょっと待って スタンバイ状態
Wait a minute, standby state.
踊る 踊る oh DANCIN' NIGHT YEAH!
Dance, dance, oh DANCIN' NIGHT YEAH!
ジャストフィットなリズムを出して
Put out a rhythm that fits just right.
唸りあげる oh SINGIN' NOW YEAH!
Cranking it up, oh SINGIN' NOW YEAH!
アイツよりも高く歌いたい
I want to sing higher than that guy.
惚れた腫れたの七色侍
The Seven-Colored Samurai of falling in and out of love.
洗いざらい主張する存在
An existence that asserts everything.
思い違いが透けてる塩梅
A state where misunderstandings are transparent.
怖いくらいのWKTK状態
A "Waku-Teka" state that's almost scary.
気にしないのがあなたのポリシー？
Is it your policy to not care?
悩んでいてもお腹は減るし
Even if you're worried, you still get hungry
なんだかんだで世間はヘルシー
In one way or another, the world is healthy
お気を確かに ぬるま湯脱皮ー
Get a grip, molting from the lukewarm water
Uhhh... Wow!
もうちょっとでスキマ埋まるのに
The gaps were almost filled
なのにね
And yet...
どうやってもうまくいかね
Doesn't work out no matter what I do
ああ もう 時間が
Ah, time is already...
足りない
Running out
座る 座る Oh SIT DOWN PLEASE
Sit down, sit down, oh SIT DOWN PLEASE
フィードバックに体預けて
Entrusting your body to the feedback
廻る 廻る Oh TURN IT AROUND
Turn, turn, oh TURN IT AROUND
唸りを上げて モーター状態
Roaring like a motor
踊る 踊る Oh DANCIN' NIGHT
Dance, dance, oh DANCIN' NIGHT
マッシュアップでもれなくアガる
Mix it up and get fired up without exception
声をあげて SINGIN' NOW
Raise your voice, SINGIN' NOW
あの子みたいなヒトになりたい
I want to be like that person
座る 座る Oh SIT DOWN PLEASE
Sit down, sit down, oh SIT DOWN PLEASE
(UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A A B A B)
廻る 廻る Oh TURN IT AROUND
Turn, turn, oh TURN IT AROUND
(L R L R STOP & DASH & L R L R STOP & DASH)
踊る 踊る Oh DANCIN' NIGHT
Dance, dance, oh DANCIN' NIGHT
(UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A A B A B)
声をあげて SINGIN' NOW
Raise your voice, SINGIN' NOW
(L R L R STOP & DASH & L R L R B A B A)
あの子みたいなヒトになりたい
I want to be like that person
やったー！よかったー！
Yay! That was great!
リモコンすごかった！
Remocon was amazing!
すごかったねー！
It was amazing, wasn't it?
リモコンすごかった？
Was Remocon amazing?
フブミオもすごかったよ！
Fubumio was amazing too!
え？最後どうなってんのあれ？
Eh? What happened at the end there?
そうだよ！
Right!
わかんないよ、あれどうなったんだろうね。
I don't know, what happened with that?
あれはちょっとね、ご想像に...
That was a little... We'll leave it to...
お任せしまーす！
...your imagination!
え、いいのね？いろんな想像しちゃっていいのね？
Eh, is it okay? Can we imagine all sorts of things?
いいのね... 逆にね！
It's okay... On the contrary!
逆にね、どんな想像する気だよ。
On the contrary, what kind of things are you thinking of?
でもリモコンめちゃめちゃよかった！
But Remocon was really great!
よかった！ありがとう！
It was great! Thank you!
ちなみに言えなかった、L...R...
By the way, I couldn't say the L...R...
最後まで言えなかった。
I couldn't say it until the end.
あれ難しいよね。
That's hard, isn't it?
難しいよね。練習頑張ったよね。
It is hard. You worked hard on practicing!
頑張ったよー！
You worked hard!
さてさて、まだまだですね、もうちょっとだけ「げまずえでぃしょん」続くんですけども。
Well, well, it's not over yet, "Gamers Edition" will continue for a little longer.
その前にちょっとグッズの告知をしていこうかと。
But before that, I'd like to make a quick announcement about merchandise.
おおー！グッズが出るんですか！
Oh! Merchandise is coming out!?
グッズでございます！告知です！こちらご覧ください！
It is merchandise! An announcement! Please take a look at this!
ホロライブゲーマーズ結成記念グッズです！
Hololive Gamers Formation Anniversary Goods!
イェーイ！見ろ見ろー！
Yay! Look, look!
ということで、まずは1つ目はこちら！
So, first of all, here's the first item!
こちら！はい！アクリルスタンドです！
This! Yes! It's acrylic stands!
こちらオトッ先生に描き下ろしていただきました。
These were drawn by Ototsu-sensei for this occasion.
今回は我々サイバーでゲーマーな感じということで。
For this time, we have a cyber and gamer-like feel.
アイドル性も忘れない、凄まじいこのイラスト！
But don't forget the idol-like quality, it's an amazing illustration!
衣装も新規の...
The outfits are also new...
そうそうそう。新しい衣装を作ってもらったんだよね。
Right, right. We had new outfits made!
そうなんです、これめちゃめちゃ可愛いですよ。
That's right, these are super cute.
次もありますよ、次もポンと、おかころバージョンもございます！
There's more, here's the next one, there's also an OkaKoro version!
背景は今回のライブステージをイメージした大型パーツも付いていますので。
The background includes large parts inspired by this live stage.
4人並べると大迫力で楽しめます！
So if you line up the four of them, you can enjoy it with great impact!
完璧に4つ揃えたらいいよね。
It'll be great if you get all four!
ぜひぜひ全員分飾ってください。お願いします！
Please decorate with everyone's part. Please do!
では続いて、2つ目はこちら！カードスリーブ！
Next, the second item is this! Card sleeves!
おおー！これあれだ、サムネでも載ってた！
Oh! This is the one from the thumbnail!
そうなんです。さかなへん先生に書いていただきました！
That's right. Sakanahen-sensei drew it for us!
イェーイ！可愛いー！めちゃめちゃ可愛いですね。
Yay! Cute! These are super cute, aren't they?
こちら、一般的なカードが入るサイズとなっておりますので。使い勝手抜群でございます！
These are a size that fits general cards, so they're very practical!
60枚も入ってるのか。そうなんです、60枚。いっぱいだね。
Whoa, it contains 60 sleeves. That's right, 60. That's a lot!
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEのカードも入ります！
Hololive Official Card Game cards also fit!
確かに、ホロカ！最近ホロカいっぱい出てるもんね。
Indeed, HoloCa! HoloCa has been releasing a lot lately.
ぜひとも好きに使ってください。必要性ある。
Please use them however you like. There's a need for these.
さてさて続いて3つ目はこちら！ラバーマット！
Now then, for the third item, here it is! Rubber mat!
こちらスリーブとお揃いとなっております。最高。
This matches the sleeves. The best.
これはゲーマーズ好きな人はたまらないね。たまらん、たまらん。
People who like Gamers will love this. Can't resist, can't resist.
このラバーマット、ホロカでも使っていただきたいですね。確かに。
I'd definitely like you to use this rubber mat for HoloCa too. For sure.
対戦でもぜひぜひご利用ください。可愛いー。欲しいよねー。
Please use it in battles too. Cute! We want it, don't we?
運営さんください。
Staff, please hand it over.
お願いします。
Please.
送ってください。
Please send it out.
そして、4つ目はこちら！
And the fourth item is this!
キャップ！
A cap!
これさ、もうロゴがね、我々のこんな入ってるんですけども...
Look, our logo is featured on it like this...
内側のところは、うちのところ『SMOK』ならぬ『FMOK』が入ってます！
And on the inside, instead of 'SMOK', it says 'FMOK'!
本当だ！あれ？
It's true! Wait, what?
『FMOK』になってます。
It's been changed to 'FMOK'.
ここ『ゲーマーズ』で良かったのではとも思うが...
I can't help but think 'Gamers' would have worked too...
そうなんですよ。なぜか『FMOK』になってる。
Exactly. For some reason, it's 'FMOK'.
これあの『SMOK』好きな方は、あのFをSにしてください。
For those of you who like 'SMOK', please just change the 'F' to an 'S'.
台無しだよ！そんなことないよ！
You're ruining it! No way!
台無しにしないでください！
Please don't ruin it!
はい、お願いします。これ横にね、コントローラーも付いているのでね...
Yes, please. It also has a controller on the side...
本当に我々ゲーマーズらしい、えーキャップとなっております。
...so it's a cap that really feels like us Gamers.
耳入るかな？
I wonder if my ears will fit.
ちょっと我々は、ちょっと厳しいかもしれん。
It might be a bit of a tight squeeze for us.
ちょっとね、潰さないといけない。
Yeah, we might have to squash them down.
コロネはギリ入るかな？
Korone's might barely fit.
あ、大丈夫。潰れてるから、もう。潰せば入る。
Oh, it's fine. They're already flat. They'll fit if I squash 'em.
ミオしゃはヤバいかもしれん。
Mio-sha's might be in trouble.
耳ティッシュだから大丈夫。
Her ears are made of tissue, so it's fine.
ティッシュ！？痛いよ絶対！
Tissue!? That's definitely going to hurt!
そして、そして！最後はこちらでございます！
And then, and then! Here is the final item!
ブロマイドケース！
A bromide case!
今回のサムネイルを使ったブロマイドと...
It comes with a bromide using today's thumbnail, and...
我々からの、えー複製メッセージが入っております。
...it includes printed messages from all of us.
ね、中身は届いてからのお楽しみとなっておりますので...
Please look forward to finding out what's inside once it arrives...
ぜひ手に入れて確認してください。
...so please get one and check it out for yourself.
何て書いたかな？ちょっと忘れちゃった。
I wonder what I wrote? I kind of forgot.
忘れちゃったよ！
I forgot, too!
嘘！ファンの皆さんにあてたじゃないか！
No way! You wrote it for all the fans!
ぜひ皆さん教えてね。
Everyone, please let us know what it says.
えーということで、えーグッズの告知はこちらで以上でございます。
And with that, that's all for the merchandise announcement.
今回ですね、フルセットの販売がございませんので...
Now, there won't be a 'Full Set' for sale this time...
欲しいものを単体で、えーご購入ください。
...so please purchase the items you want individually.
はい、数量限定もないのでね...
And since there are no limited quantities...
じっくりじっくり、あの考えてたくさんお迎えしてくれると嬉しいです。
...I'd be happy if you took your time to think and get plenty of them.
でも、きっと受注期間はあるよね？
But I'm sure there's a pre-order period, right?
まあ多分あると思います。1年は考えられないかなって感じ。
Yeah, most likely. You probably can't take a whole year to decide.
詳細はグッズ販売ページからご確認をお願いします。
Please check the merchandise sales page for more details.
そしてそして、ちょっと個人的な告知が白上もございます。
And also, I, Shirakami, have a personal announcement to make!
ありがたいことに2025年2月13日に、白上フブキソロライブ...
Gratefully, on February 13th, 2025, the Shirakami Fubuki Solo Live...
『FBKINGDOM ANTHIA』がぴあアリーナMMにて開催でございます！
...'FBKINGDOM ANTHIA' will be held at Pia Arena MM!
昨日、ゲストの告知もしまして、さくらみこちが来てくれることになりました！
And yesterday, I also announced the guest—Sakura Miko-chi will be joining me!
こちらですね、二次先行あのチケットがですね、申し込みがですね...
For this, the secondary early ticket applications...
明日、明日の23時59分となっておりますので、よろしくお願いします。
...will end tomorrow at 23:59, so please keep that in mind.
明日開始なの？二次先行。
They start tomorrow? The secondary early tickets.
明日終わり。
They end tomorrow.
終わりなの！？じゃあ今じゃん！
They end!? Then it's right now!
今もうすぐやったほうがいい。
Yes, you should do it right away.
ということで、えーライブももう終盤でございますね。
And with that, the live is now in its final stages.
ラスト、ラスト1曲！
One last song!
えー、もう終わり！？1曲残してんのかい！
What, already over!? You only have one song left!?
あれ？なんかまだ歌ってないやつあるんじゃない？ありますね。
Wait, isn't there a song we haven't sung yet? There is.
まあなんですけども、ちょっと改めて我々今回6周年迎えたということで...
But anyway, since we've reached our 6th anniversary...
それぞれ一言ずつね、まあ今まで振り返りでもいいし、また来年に向けてでもいいので...
...let's each say a few words, reflecting on the past or looking toward next year.
一言ずつじゃあちょっとミオからいいですか？うちは2024年は...
Mio, would you like to go first? Well, for me, 2024 was...
ゲーマーズのねイベントとかあったのにさ...
...even though there were Gamers events and all...
うちは出れなかったっていうこととかあったので、ちょっと悲しい年になってしまったんですけど...
...I couldn't participate, so it ended up being a bit of a sad year.
2025年は、ゲーマーズのみんなと一緒に最高の年にしたいなって思っているので...
So in 2025, I want to make it the best year ever with everyone in Gamers...
頑張って健康的に過ごしたいなって思ってます！
...so I'll do my best to stay healthy!
よろしくね、みんな。2025年。
So please count on me in 2025, everyone!
白上もね、2024年はあの超超超ゲーマーズもありましてね...
For me too, 2024 had 'Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers'...
もっと残念ながらねミオが参加できなかったので、まあ来年再来年とかを目指してね...
...and since Mio unfortunately couldn't join, looking toward next year or the year after...
このゲーマーズでまた頑張って『超超超ゲーマーズ2』をね開催できるようにしていきたいと思っております。
...I want us to work hard as Gamers so we can hold 'Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2'!
やりたいけど、そんな簡単にやろうってできるようなもんじゃないからさ... やらせてください！
I want to, but it's not the kind of thing you can just easily do... Please let us do it!
お願いします。頑張ります。まあオンラインはね、今日あれとして...
Please. We'll work hard. Today was an online event, but...
オフラインをまた目指して、えー頑張っていきたいと思います！
...I want to aim for an offline event again and do our best!
いや、もう6周年ですか。早いですね。早いよね。
Wow, it's already our 6th anniversary. Time flies! It really does!
そんな気する？しない！だよね。
Does it feel like that? Not at all! Right?
7年目くらいの気持ちでいるけどね。
Though I feel like it's been about seven years.
まさかの！
No way!
新人、新人！
Freshmen, freshmen!
そうだよ。
That's right.
まだまだ気持ちは新人。
Our hearts are still those of freshmen.
初心を忘れずにね。
Never forget your beginner's heart.
そうだね。
True.
さあ、頑張っていきたいと思っていますよ、やはり。
Well, I still want to keep doing my best.
おー、本当に「抱っこしてください」って感じだよね。
Oh, it's really like, "Please carry me."
おんぶに抱っこ？
A free ride?
どういうこと？
What do you mean?
おかころでってこと？
You mean as OkaKoro?
さあ。
Well...
おかころおんぶ抱っこなの？
Is OkaKoro a free ride?
え、おかゆん、これ背負えるの？
Eh, Okayu-n, can you carry this?
あとで試そう、あとで。
Let's try it later.
物理的になんだね。
Oh, it's physical.
さあ、なるほどね。
I see.
さあ、でもみおちゃんも言ってましたけど、
Well, as Mio-chan was saying...
みんなでね、
...with everyone...
また楽しいゲマズ生活を送りたいと思っておりますよ。
...I want to continue having a fun Gamers life.
いや、2025年も楽しい1年にしようぜ！
Let's make 2025 a fun year too!
さてさて、じゃあ続いて、ころね！
Now then, next is Korone!
あ、ころねはー、
Ah, as for Korone...
ゲマズともっと遊びたい！
I want to play more with Gamers!
いいじゃん、遊びたい！
That's great, let's play!
なんかコラボさ、最近さ、多いよね。前は1年に1回集まればいいほうだったのに。
We've had more collabs lately. Before, we were lucky to meet once a year.
ちょっと増えてきたよね。
It has increased a bit.
確かに、ちょっと増えたよね。
True, it has increased a bit.
裏ある？
Is there an ulterior motive?
裏ってどういうこと？
What do you mean by that?
何、何？
What, what?
裏表ないの？ 大丈夫？
No two sides to it? Are you sure?
ないよ、ないよ！
No, no!
普通に仲良くしてるだけだよね。
We're just getting along normally.
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
怖いよ！ 裏を考えないでよ！
That's scary! Don't look for hidden meanings!
裏がなかったら、お前みおに唾吐いたりしねーだろ！
If there wasn't a hidden side, you wouldn't spit on Mio!
はい、失礼しましたー。
Right, excuse me.
ということで、結局？
So, in the end?
結局何が言いたいの？
What did you want to say in the end?
来年も、仲良く4人で活動、
Next year too, the four of us will work together...
あ、来年も？
Ah, next year too?
来年も、4人で仲良く活動していきましょう！
Next year too, let's the four of us continue to work well together!
素晴らしい、素晴らしい！
Wonderful, wonderful!
あとプラスリスナーさんもね。
And our listeners too.
そうです、そうです。
Yes, that's right.
これからも、ホロライブゲーマーズ、ファンの皆さんと共々によろしくお願いいたします。
From here on out, we look forward to your continued support for Hololive Gamers and our fans.
お願いします！
Thank you!
さて、じゃあみんな言い残すことはないかい？
Now then, does anyone have anything left to say?
ないぞー！
Nothing!
よーし、じゃあ最後に一曲行っちゃいますよ！
Alright, then let's go with one last song!
はい！
Yes!
ということでね、今回まだライブで使っていないこの前のステージに行って、
And so, we'll head to that stage over there that we haven't used yet...
ちょっとお着替えもして、みんなで歌いたいと思います！
...and we'll change our outfits and sing for everyone!
行くぞ、ステージへ！
Let's go to the stage!
『ホロライブゲーマーズ！！』
"Hololive Gamers!!"
We are GAMERS!!!!
こーんとキツネが登場
A fox appears with a "kon"
白上ケモ耳白上フブキです
White-haired, animal-eared, I'm Shirakami Fubuki
突っ込んでなきゃ始まらない
It won't start without a comeback
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukon-bu too
Hi Friends!!
Yeah!!
古今東西コーン茶ちょうだい
Past and present, give me corn tea
AIじゃないし得意はMC
I'm not AI, and my specialty is MCing
赤い恋人より金の仲良し
Closer to the golden one than the red lover
ミョー！
Myo!
うちうちうちだよ大神ミオだよ
It's me, me, me, I'm Ookami Mio
黒髪ケモ耳狼
Black-haired, animal-eared wolf
突っ込んで止めます Like a ママ
I'll stop you with a comeback like a mom
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop, cackling
つまり実はPONってコト！？
So that means I'm actually clumsy?!
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of small-foot steps
タロット占いで見る未来
The future seen through tarot reading
ホラーゲームはやりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲマズ最強
With the four of us together, Gamers are the strongest
君も遊ぼおよ Bダッシュ
Let's play together, B-dash
クリア目指してレベル上げ今日は
Leveling up to aim for a clear, today...
今日は何プレイしよ
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll capture your heart too
選択肢をしてシミュレーション
Make a choice and simulate
初見も古参も大変よやっぱ
First-timers and veterans, it's tough as expected
ビデオゲームは楽しいね
Video games are fun, aren't they?
We are GAMERS!!!!
あそこ！
Over there!
いっくよーもぐもぐー
Here I go, munch munch
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
おにぎりおにぎり はいどーぞ
Onigiri, onigiri, here you go
ゆらゆらふらふら しゃーない猫だもん
Swaying, wobbling, I'm just a cat, can't help it
ふーん そっか お前でよくない？
Hmm, I see. Wouldn't you be fine?
まったりゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Relaxed and slow, bouncing rhythm
全肯定する おかゆイズム
The all-affirming Okayu-ism
全工程 効率OK
All processes, efficiency OK
毎日僕とい〜っしょ！
Every day, be with me!
ころね！
Korone!
おあよー ゆびゆび ワンワン
Oayo! Yubi-yubi! Woof woof!
パンもふこふこ 戌神ころね
Fluffy bread too, Inugami Korone
チャンネル登録 スパチャにエナドリ
山ほど摂取して熱く活け
Channel subs, Super Chats, and energy drinks
Consume them in spades and live passionately
詰まるイントネーション 割れるリアクション
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信ショー
Stumbling intonation, cracked reactions
First, will you offer up your fingers? Stream show
わかった なあほーね 指示厨OK
好物のレトロゲーお届け
Got it, I see; backseat drivers OK
Delivering your favorite retro games
四人そろえば ゲーマーズ最高
フラグが立てば 即回収
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the best
If a flag is raised, we collect it instantly
エイム鍛えて 狙い撃ち
今日は何プレイしよう？
Train your aim and take the shot
What should we play today?
君のハートを 回復しちゃう
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
I'll restore your heart
This dungeon is so exciting, isn't it?
耐え切って言うか やめられない
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
I can't endure it—I mean, I can't stop
Because I just love games so much!
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。」
"Suddenly, it's time for the Bonus Challenge."
「大きな声でレスポンスして高得点を狙いましょう！」
"Respond with a loud voice and aim for a high score!"
Say!! こーんこんっ！
Say!! Kon kon!
(こーんこんっ！)
(Kon kon!)
Say!! みおーんみおーん！
Say!! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーんみおーん！)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
Say!! もぐもぐっ！
Say!! Mogu mogu!
(もぐもぐっ！)
(Mogu mogu!)
Say!! ゆびゆびっ！
Say!! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびゆびっ！)
(Yubi yubi!)
Say!! こーんこんっ！
Say!! Kon kon!
(こーんこんっ！)
(Kon kon!)
Say!! みおーんみおーん！
Say!! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーんみおーん！)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
Say!! もぐもぐっ！
Say!! Mogu mogu!
(もぐもぐっ！)
(Mogu mogu!)
Say!! ゆびゆびっ！
Say!! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびゆびっ！)
(Yubi yubi!)
PERFECT!! おおー！！！
PERFECT!! Ohhh!!!
四人そろえば ゲーマーズ最強
うまくいかなくってもコンティニュー
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the strongest
Even if things don't go well, we continue
全クリするまで 諦めない
エンディングを見に行こう
We won't give up until the final clear
Let's go see the ending
君のハートを 攻略しちゃう
選択をして シミュレーション
I'll conquer your heart
Make your choice—simulation
初見も常連も 大歓迎
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
First-timers and regulars are all welcome
As expected, games are fun
We are GAMERS!!!!
こうして世界の平和は訪れたのであったー
And thus, peace was restored to the world.
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
ちょっと違くないか？
Isn't that a little off?
サンタ衣装だったからね
Well, we were in Santa outfits.
ということで、3D LIVE ありがとうございました！
So, thank you for the 3D LIVE!
今年も良い年だったけど、来年もゲーマーズのみんなで良い年にしましょう！
It's been a great year, but let's make next year a great one for Gamers too!
オー！/ はい！
Oh! / Yes!
リスナーのみんなもついてきてね、2025年！
Listeners, please keep following us in 2025!
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
来年もやりたいよね、ライブ
I want to do a live next year too.
やりたーい！/ やろうやろう！
I want to! / Let's do it, let's do it!
ということで、ありがとうございましたー！
So, thank you very much!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!